<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Stefano Mangini</title><link>https://stefanomangini.com/</link><description>Stefano Mangini's personal website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>mangini.stfn@gmail.com (Stefano Mangini)</managingEditor><webMaster>mangini.stfn@gmail.com (Stefano Mangini)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stefanomangini.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My bookshelf</title><link>https://stefanomangini.com/books/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://stefanomangini.com/books/</guid><description><![CDATA[My bookshelf Here&rsquo;s my virtual bookshelf: a list of books I&rsquo;ve been reading lately and books I wish to read in the future! This is mostly for personal records, but maybe you can get inspired by some of the books in the list! Also, I&rsquo;m always open to new suggestions, so contact me if you have one!
Now reading 📖 : The Emperor&rsquo;s new mind, by Roger Penrose.
To read  Thinking, Fast and Slow, by Daniel Kahneman.]]></description></item><item><title>What is Quantum Machine Learning?</title><link>https://stefanomangini.com/endofyearphd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 16:45:40 +0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://stefanomangini.com/endofyearphd/</guid><description>What is Quantum Machine Learning? Yesterday I took part in the End of Year seminars of PhD students at University of Pavia. For the end of my first year, I had to I talk about my research field, Quantum Machine Learning, introducing the state of the art, drawbacks and future possibilities.
Here is my presentation, go check it out: presentation.
😉</description></item><item><title>Food Choices and Sustainability</title><link>https://stefanomangini.com/ilgrandemacello/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 16:45:40 +0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://stefanomangini.com/ilgrandemacello/</guid><description><![CDATA[Download article &ldquo;Il Grande Macello&rdquo;, by Stefano Mangini <i class="fas fa-file-download"></i>
 Food Choices and Sustainability Few months ago, I decided to wrote a divulgation article on food choices and sustainability, explaining those reasons which motivated me to approach a full plant based diet. Unfortunately, the article was targeted to an Italian audience and it is then written in Italian, because you can already find great resources and information on the topic in english.]]></description></item><item><title>Welcome to my blog!</title><link>https://stefanomangini.com/welcome/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 16:45:40 +0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://stefanomangini.com/welcome/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog! Here I will try to publish interesting content about my research, thoughts and experiences! See you soon!</description></item></channel></rss>